yeahmobi.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy Policy | Yeahmobi

Last Updated:December 17, 2018

Yeahmobi is committed to respecting and protecting individuals’ privacy rights. This Privacy Policy explains how Click Tech Limited, its subsidiaries and affiliated companies (collectively, “Yeahmobi” or “we”, “us”, “our”) collect, use, secure end user (“you” or “your”) information.

Yeahmobi provides various internet services including but not limited to mobile advertising (“Services”). We collect information from users when users (i) visit our website; (ii) view ads served by our advertising service; (iii) interact with our advertising service; or (iv) interact with the platforms, applications, websites or any other service provided by our business partners (e.g. app publisher, advertiser) .

Please review this Privacy Policy before using our Services or visiting our website. We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. The amended Privacy Policy will be displayed on our site. Please check our Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you have read the latest version. Continued use of the Services after the effective date will be your acknowledgement that have accepted the revised Privacy Policy.

 **1\. What information is collected and how it is collected?**  
We may collect the following information from or about our users when they access our Services.  
• information which users provide to us, for example users’ name and email address;  
• information automatically collected when users use the Services, such as users’ browser information (user agent), IP host address, mobile device type, the Identifier for Advertising (IDFA) and other device identifiers. We also use cookies to collect certain information about users. Cookies collect information on the device and network used to access the domain, and the date and time that users access the domain. This information is for internal use only, such as optimizing performance of the Services. The information cannot identify the individual user.  
• information from other third party partners of Yeahmobi, such as companies that provide services to us and our business partners. Furthermore, the following partners may receive data from users and their interactions with our Services: Unity Technologies ( Privacy Policy located at: <https://unity3d.com/legal/privacy-policy>) .However, our agreements with these service providers limit the types of information these companies collect, how they may collect it, and how they may use it.

 **2\. What does Yeahmobi do with the Information?**  
We use the information, including any personal information, provided by users to provide the Services and for internal business purposes, such as improving our services; compiling aggregate data for internal and external business purposes; preventing potentially illegal activities; in support of user accounts or customer service requests; in relation with any required governmental or legal action; and other uses in accordance with our advertising services’ respective Terms and Conditions.  
We may share your personal information with our business partners, including advertisers, data tracking companies, and with Yeahmobi affiliates so that we can better provide advertising that is relevant to you. When users are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), personal information collected from users, will be transferred to recipients in countries located outside the EEA (including US, Brazil, Singapore), which may not provide a similar or adequate level of protection to that provided by countries in the EEA. We will take reasonable measures to protect user information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Where required by law, the publisher and/or advertiser will obtain user consent to the transfer of user personal information to recipients, as described in this Privacy Policy, which are located outside the EEA. You may withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us at dataprivacy@yeahmobi.com.

 **3\. How does Yeahmobi protect the Information?**  
We use appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect the information we collect. We use multiple electronic, procedural, and physical security measures to protect against unauthorized or unlawful use or alteration of information, and against any accidental loss, destruction, or damage to information.  
We also have a Data Protection Officer (“DPO”) according to GDPR. The DPO is responsible for monitoring our compliance with GDPR and cooperating with supervisory authority. His contact is dataprivacy@yeahmobi.com.

 **4\. How long do we keep information for?**  
We may retain the information relating to a user device collected from partnering mobile publishers or app developers for as long as a user uses the Services and for the purposes as stated in this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise required by law or applicable contract. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Yeahmobi may retain and use such information in a non-identifiable, aggregated format, as necessary for internal analytical purposes, to comply with its legal obligations, to resolve disputes and enforce agreements. Yeahmobi will make efforts to guarantee that personal information is kept for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal information is processed.

 **5\. User Rights to their information**  
Users have certain choices available to them when it comes to their information. For residents of the EU, we collect and process information about the users who live in the EEA only on where we have legal bases under applicable EU laws. For EU users, you have the rights to request a copy of their information, to object to our use of their information, to request the deletion or restriction of their information unless subject to a legal hold, or to request their information in a structured, electronic format. Furthermore, they may withdraw their consent to our processing of their information at any time by contacting as dataprivacy@yeahmobi.com, but that will mean we can no longer provide the Services to the user.

 **6\. Yeahmobi policy towards children**  
Yeahmobi has always adopted a policy of not knowingly collecting any personal information about children under the age of 13 and if we become aware that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database.

 **7\. Additional Choices for California Residents**  
If a user is a California resident, user may be entitled to request certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties who wish to contact the user or send promotional information about their products and services. If a user is a California resident and would like to request a copy of information regarding our disclosure to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year, user can send a request to dataprivacy@yeahmobi.com.

 **8\. Send “Do Not Track” Signals:**  
Some browsers have incorporated “Do Not Track” (DNT) features that can send a signal to the websites a user visits indicating user does not wish to be tracked. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret the DNT signal, our Services do not currently respond to browser DNT signals.

 **9\. Can users opt out of cookies?**  
Yeahmobi may use cookies, or other technology (collectively “Cookies”) to collect certain information about you when you are visiting the Site. Cookies are small text files that are stored automatically on your browser by a website during your visit. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. The purpose of Cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save your time. By using the Site, you consent to the use of the Cookies. If you do not accept these Cookies, you can change your browser’s settings to delete cookies that have already been set and to not accept new Cookies. Please note, however, if you delete Cookies or do not accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.

 **10\. Can users opt out of devices?**  
Yeahmobi respects your privacy as a user, and you can opt-out from receiving interest-based advertising from Yeahmobi on supported devices:  
You can opt out of having your Mobile IDs used for certain types of interest-based mobile advertising (also called “cross-app advertising”), including those performed by Yeahmobi, by accessing the settings on your Apple or Android mobile device, as follows:  
Apple Devices: If you have an Apple device, you can opt out of most cross-app advertising by updating to iOS 6.0 or higher and enabling “Limit Ad Tracking.”  
iOS 7 and Higher: Go to Settings → Privacy → Advertising, and toggle “Limit Ad Tracking” to ‘ON.’  
iOS 6: Go to Settings → General → About → Advertising, and toggle “Limit Ad Tracking” to ‘ON.’  
More information about the iOS setting can be found here: https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074  
Android Devices: If you have an Android device, you can opt out of most cross-app advertising by going to Google Settings → Ads, and selecting the option to opt out of interest-based ads.  
When you have opted out using this setting on a device, Yeahmobi will not use in-app information collected from that device to infer your interests or serve ads to that device that are targeted based on your inferred interests.  
These platforms control how these settings work, so the above instructions may change, and the precise language may be different on certain (particularly, on older) devices. Likewise, if your device uses other platforms not described above, please check the settings for those devices.  
Please note that while opting out limits Yeahmobi collection of information to serve you ads based on your inferred interests, it does not prevent you from receiving ads from Yeahmobi, Facebook, Google, or third parties.”  
If you have any queries regarding Privacy Policy, please do contact us at dataprivacy@yeahmobi.com.
